out and that's where I'm at I'm a
student so I can be a teacher and what
I'm doing Ryan see is I'm I'm plugging
in I'm learning and then I'm simply
putting that information back out to the
youth in a way that the youth can
understand it because it's very scary
when you get out of high school some
people just want to party like you said
some people want to go to school and the
way I approach it is don't go to school
because your parents tell you to go to
school if you plan on going to school go
to school to do what you want to do
because if you're not chasing your true
dreams and you're not chasing uh what
you want to do in life then there's no
point of doing it like your chances of
even existing on this Earth is one in
five trillion so act like it go after it
and get it and as far as the partying
goes my opinion on that is what are you
celebrating when I get to the top when I
reach the Pinnacle of success then there
will be time for pardoning but until now
a little
bit and um and then bring it up so that
you could see yeah there we oh yeah
we're good and we are good so uh how's
it going my friend it's going good my
man you know how I do it man always on
the grind focusing on what I got to do
uh to pursue better opportunities with
my business coming up in 2017 and just
reaching out my man that's great so
folks Welcome to the hustle Zone you
know the hustle zone is not uh like when
it comes down to the hustle Zone it's
not the hustle zone until I do welcome
to the hustle zone right because it's
all about energy it's all about passion
and you know the thing about the great
thing about the hustle zone is that we
bring it to you raw you know we we talk
about the things that most people won't
talk about entrepreneurialism you know
uh David body told me you know the
hustle Zone tells the tells the story
not the glory you know because everyone
has a path to from getting from point A
to point B and um you know so this is
I'm really excited to to to be here to
hear this young man's story um you know
I've uh we've been friends for for a
little time here on Facebook and all of
a sudden overnight Young Gun
motivation just pops up and then you
have you know this man on here and he's
interviewing people he's giving people
motivation you know he he seems to be
headstrong he seems to have a lot of
like energy and a lot of wisdom for for
for being someone that it it you know is
18 years old I remember when I was 17 17
years old starting my own business and U
you know a lot of people were
discouraging me when I was growing up
and so we're it's it's and look where
I've become without giving up right so
you know we got Stephen Graber how are
you doing my friend I'm doing good my
man I'm doing good I I I should say I'm
doing phenomenal I've never been better
I've got this business coming up January
1st of 2017 Young Gun motivation I've
been doing a lot of the prep work laying
down the foundational plans and really
just starting to get rolling connecting
with other entrepreneurs motivational
speakers and social media influencers
and I'm just going after it and I'm
getting it because come 2017 we're going
to hit it with all we got nice nice
so um let's start let's start from um
like we're we're going to do this cuz
like this I feel like this hustle Zone I
was excited for this hustle Zone uh
because I I really want um to send a
message out to the youth and and people
that um you know are just starting their
lives just getting out of high school
and um a lot a lot of Youth don't have
Direction a lot of them don't know what
they're doing and um you know some of
them want to have fun and someone some
of them want to um you know want to go
back to school so where do you fall in
that those those
categories well I neither party or I am
not currently in college instead I'm
deciding to pursue other opportunities
like I said with young gun motivation
I'm going after it and I'm getting it
and I'm taking what I have learned and
you know uh I look at my my life and my
company like a light bulb right I plug
into information so I can put
information out and that's where I'm at
I'm a student so I can be a teacher and
what I'm doing Ryan see is I'm I'm
plugging in I'm learning and then I'm
simply putting that information back out
to the youth in the way that the youth
can understand it because it's very
scary when you get out of high school
some people just want to party like you
said some people want to go to school
and the way I approach it is don't go to
school because your parents tell you to
go to school if you plan on going to
school go to school to do what you want
to do because if you're not chasing your
true dreams and you're not tracing uh
what you want to do in life then there's
no point of doing it like your chances
of even existing on this Earth is one in
five trillion so act like it go after it
and get it and as far as the partying
goes my opinion on that is what are you
celebrating when I get to the top when I
reach the Pinnacle of success then there
will be time for Harding but until now
until that point I'm going to keep
hustling it I'm going to wake up every
day and I'm going to go after it and I'm
going to get it yeah that's awesome bro
and um you you seem pretty pumped up and
you seem uh pretty driven so let's talk
about like like like where are you
getting you know the the entrepreneurial
Spirit like where is that all coming
from my drive and my my why is my my
purpose man is I look around and I see
all these Youth and and you know in in
suburb areas into the inner cities Youth
and I see that my generation is in
trouble if people in my group right the
youth group don't start standing up and
and teaching because the thing is is
everything is learning information
changes situation so uh it's time that
we need to stand up plug information
into these Youth and change their lives
because we are the future of this earth
right and it's time that we start
stepping up stop partying and moving
forward with our life and and back to
your question Ryan about uh what drives
me man it's just looking around and
seeing where my generation is
headed and looking at the alternative
where we could be headed and they're two
totally separate roads and I believe
that people like me young entrepreneurs
young motivational speakers like myself
young people who are not afraid to stand
up against the current or stand up
against the crowd to rise up and tell
them hey we don't have to go this path
there's a lot better options and there's
a lot better choices out there in life
now did you um have parents that were
entrepreneurs like what's like tell me a
little bit about your I did not Ryan I
did not in fact uh my my mom and dad
both tell me I have no clue where you
get your sales person personality from I
have no clue where you get your attitude
towards things because my mom was a
preschool teacher and my dad is a
construction worker so oh wow and so
what what like what motivated you to uh
um to to just start this thing like what
what was the thing that kind of gave you
that ump well uh tuning into to Grant
Cardone uh he was a big factor a big one
of my my uh
the people who have encouraged me Grant
Cardone uh Dr Eric Thomas uh even Coach
Frank sagasta if you don't know him
check him out file him uh follow him and
stuff but but just these great people
man they pumped me with information they
got me fired up and they taught me they
totally turned my cheek the other way
like whoa this is the way that you
achieve success this is the way that you
make things happen and they really
opened my eyes up and showed me what I
want to do with my life
okay wow and so how did you how did you
meet Frank and how did you meet everyone
uh uh Coach Frank sagasta was my
football coach in high school oh so
you're like wow so he was your football
coach so so tell me a little bit about
Frank so so Coach Frank sagasa you know
he's an amazing man he taught me a lot
uh I was those type of people in high
school and growing up that I didn't care
about nothing I thought the world owed
me everything and he totally just uh
changed my view of life he pushed me
through football taught me to never quit
and just altogether a phenomenal guy
phenomenal mentor and you know he puts
everything on the line every single day
and uh changes people's lives gives 120%
in each and everything that he does and
uh basically like I said he was a
phenomenal mentor and just observing the
way he approached life and plus the
teachings that he gave me it totally
completely
120% changed my life so had had had you
not been
um had you not been in the situation
where you met a a guy like Frank where
would you
be uh honestly to be honest with you I
would probably still be the rockhead kid
that I was uh wanting to fight everybody
uh had the mentality you know uh screw
the world you know everybody owes me
everything um and and that's just simply
not the case Ryan see the case is is
that if you want something you got to go
out and get it yourself because the
world owes you nothing so take what you
have right we have a gift to give it
away take what you have give it away you
got to be the change that you want to
see in the
world now do you have like how's your
friends take this this new um you know I
I wouldn't say that this is new this is
a part of you but like how are your
friends receiving this like people in
your age category some of them embrace
it and some of them completely criticize
and discriminate it it just depends on
the person it depends on the standpoint
I've had a lot of positive things happen
and I've had a lot of negative things uh
happen but see both as a motivational
speaker and an entrepreneur if anything
negative happens I've learned that I had
to cut out the negative because if you
have negativity running your life you
just cannot move forward you got to cut
the negative negativity out around
yourself around the people that
encourage you that uplift you and and
you know pretty much just help you move
forward and that's who your true friends
are you know uh the the friends that are
sitting there criticizing you telling
you you'll never make it telling you you
know putting you down all the time and
they're not true friends you got to
surround yourself around people that are
going to encourage you to move forward
with your life better your life and just
alog together like Grant Cardone says
10x your life so now I hear a lot of
buzzword a lot of quotes Grant Cardone
yada yada yada now a lot of people are
going to say well hey this guy's an
18-year-old kid what does he know about
success what does he know about
achieving anything like what what was
your response in regards to that my
response to them is very very simple
Ryan and that's the fact that I have
tuned into information right I've
completely plugged in I I've read books
by Grant Cardone average skill or Eric
Thomas average skill phenomenal will
Grant Cardone be obsessed be average you
know I've just completely 10x My Life by
plugging into information and
information truly does change situations
and this information uh has totally
changed my mindset with business totally
changed my mindset with life you know I
read a book earlier in the year by um
um trying to remember his name anyways
the name of the book was uh how to win
friends and influence others it was by
um Napoleon not Napoleon Hill but uh uh
not Stephen cvy what is his name
Carnegie yeah no Dale Carnegie Dale
Carnegie okay yeah I knew it was
somewhere around those lines but anyways
it's just it's just tuning into
information Ryan and reading books and
and that's what I encourage each and
every one of you to do just tune in
information you know uh I've studied a
lot about Gandhi if you don't know who
he he who he was and his influence
impact on the world and just different
great phenomenal people and what happens
Ryan is when you start looking at people
like Grant Cardone Eric Thomas uh gandi
you know you can look at Tony Robbins
anybody you consider great and you truly
research them and tune into their
information you start to notice that
there's a pattern there's a road that
there's that there's pavement there's
actually uh ground ground you know
pounded in the ground ways to be
successful start to notice that pattern
that each successful person took to
become successful and you just continue
on that road that they took okay but you
know and I get that I get that however
like what have you done for you to be
considered a successful person or how do
you define the success that you've
already had you know because I mean like
and I'm going to just give you some like
some context here not to bring it down
or or anything like that cuz this is
just it just gives people a ability to
understand like who you are um
absolutely you know you know there's a
lot of people out there that just coming
on camera and just motivating people and
not really giving they're giving stuff
that they quote from other books and
whatnot but they're not really giving
their true experiences and they're not
really demonstrating um how they've um
how they've uh
succeeded right I think we all get into
that habit of we do more talking and
we're not really living our life and in
what ways have you like you know like
like give me a few examples of stuff
that you've learned in these books and
and have you applied them have you um uh
you know have you like let's say Grant
Cardone says you know set goals and all
that stuff like what are the sort of the
actions that you took um or that you've
taken uh to to get to this point okay
absolutely so so one of the things that
I've learned is massive effective action
talk is cheap but action is like golden
nuggets so the things that I've done you
know Grant Cardone talks about uh turn
your turn your dreams into goals your
goals into plans follow through with
those plans and they'll turn into
reality right so I had a dream about
Young Gun motivation I wanted to create
this phenomenal company put it together
and go out go after it and influence
teens and young adults to change their
lives to get off the drugs to set their
mind straight right that was my dream so
I turned it into a goal well I broke
that goal down and I set it into a plan
I'm currently in the execution of that
plan part um I've had people come to me
uh you know I've been interviewing doing
a lot of lives with a lot of different
entrepreneurs and motivational speakers
uh you of course Ryan Perez Dave Dy
Coach Frank Saga
uh Terence Freeman I've been connecting
with a lot of entrepreneurs and great
people and now I'm going forward with my
plan and I'm executing my plan right I
have some Live Events setting up I'm
going to take Young Gun motivation on
tour we're going to go to all the high
schools we're going to go to the
churches we're going to have a lot of
live events coming out and basically
start in our community and Branch out
that's amazing bro that's amazing and
then like tell me a little bit about
your dreams like what are your goals
like what are are the things that uh you
have in because we're we're definitely
going to get you back on the husta zone
and we want you to follow up with them
so what are some of the goals that you
got so so the goal that I have right is
um I'm financially stable I'm I'm okay
financially right but I'm not I'm not
100% financially that's another one of
my goals in the future so I hold on one
second so you were financially stable
like through businesses like what how
are what makes you financially stable
like what are the things that that
you're doing right now person person
wise my income uh is I work a part-time
retail job I do inventory and I work in
the dairy department and uh other other
sources of income is I'm it works
independent distributor right I saw a
lot of medical products and medical
supplements and then the third source of
income of course is through Young Gun
motivation and that's the products that
we sell on inspirational t-shirts
inspirational wear things like that
that's amazing so I and I've seen you
you've gotten like already like the
hustle Zone we don't have any sponsors
sponsors make sure to check us out we
would love to have you in there but you
already got sponsors that's another way
we're bringing in income and when I say
income I don't necessarily mean money
there's different ways of income that
we're bringing in different types of
ways that sponsors help us out but I am
bringing in income through sponsors as
well that's amazing so we're going to
cut uh to commercial here uh and then
we'll we'll be back in
just so that people understand with that
deal $6.99 for startup website one year
free hosting five pages and then One
logo so a lot of people that that need
help starting up and remember every time
you uh you purchase a website with Bai
creative we donate a free website to a
person with a disability uh that wants
to be an entrepreneur or that is a an an
entrepreneur so hit me up send me a
message I would love to help you guys
out so going back to stepen Young Gun
motivator or motivation so tell me about
Young Gun motivation why did you choose
Young
Gun Young Gun well I'm a Young Gun Ryan
straight up like I'm 18 years old right
I'm 18 years old I got uh three
businesses really four if you want to
include young gun motivation of course
uh but I'm I'm 18 an entrepreneur a
motivational speaker a social media
influencer teaching people to go out
straight up hustle and get after it so
that's the reason why I came up with
young gun motivation and of course I am
the Young Gun motivator but that the
reason why I came up with that name is
because I'm I'm young you know and I'm
encouraging other youth see Ryan I don't
just want to help other youth but I want
to give them the steps to success and I
want to teach them uh to go out and
influence others themselves because it's
one thing to help somebody but it's a
whole another thing to teach them so
they can go out and do it themselves and
so that's where I'm at with my company
that's awesome and um what kind of
support do you have uh with your your
family like is your family full in
support of your your your business ideas
and absolutely absolutely I got some
family that is and I got some family
members that don't you know uh you you
always get criticism as an entrepreneur
you always get criticism as a as a
motivational speaker or some someone as
young as I am I go through a lot of
criticization you know I get criticized
a lot and uh some of it is by Family
some of it is by friends some of it is
by people that I don't even know you get
criticized but see my biggest issue what
what what are your what are your your
your like what are the basic criticisms
that you're receiving right
now uh pretty much that you know you're
young you don't know what you're talking
about things like that uh you know uh
keep keep talking about grinding you
don't know nothing about grinding you're
only 18 years old another thing uh that
people bring up is uh you're a big
dreamer good luck achieving it just just
simple things like that Ryan but one of
the things that I've learned over time
is to look like put my blinders on put
my my my ear muffers on right I don't
listen to nobody in fact the more they
criticize the more it drives me in fact
I read a post that one of my buddies
posted online the other day and it says
hustle and tell your hater ERS work for
you and that's where I'm at man like I
don't focus on what anybody else says I
don't focus on it I just go out get
after it and get the job done the only
thing I'm focused on is massive
effective action going out there
breaking through barriers and getting
the job done that's right I mean like
honestly like I I I I have to agree with
you that um you know because like like
if we if I listen to there I was a
rapper back in the days and I used to
like you know I used to send out my
tracks uh to people I wanted them to
hear it and then I'm and then the the
biggest thing that I would say to them
is like what's your feedback give me
your feedback and they'd be like well
this is whack this is you know I think
the base needs to be like this and your
lyrics I felt like it could be do you
know what I realized then that people
will find anything you can find anything
negative about anybody you can find
something negative about the Sun and
I've said this before my other broadcast
like the sun's too hot uh it's too
distant oh it comes up too early you
know what I mean like you can find so
many negative things um you could find
so many negative things that um about uh
somebody that you know I don't want to I
don't even welcome some of the criticism
I think you know the people that I'm
really concerned about um and that
really sometimes where I can't sleep at
night is my customers like it's it's the
people that actually buy me products
because at the end of the day those are
the people that matter and if they're
not consuming then I'm then then I'm out
of business right so you know it's not
like oh I'm going to do whatever I want
I'm doing what I what I what I want um
to the degree that it doesn't piss my
customers off you know absolutely and
one of the things that I want to bring
up and really mention is if you're a
younger person and you're watching this
the younger generation is all about the
trend right if I got my new Nikes then I
fit in if I if I got my you know what
I'm saying if I got my uh under arour
shirt on then I'm going to fit in you
know don't focus on the trend don't
focus on what everybody else is doing we
are here to not stand with the crowd but
to stand against the crowd right we're
going to get criticized it's part of
doing it but don't Focus like me and
Ryan were just talking about do not
focus on the
criticization focus on what you're doing
focus on your dream like I said earlier
dreams turn into goals turn into plans
if you act upon those plans then they
turn into reality a quote that young gun
motivation made and it's our motto and
what I'm basing this company off of and
what we believe and live off of is the
bridge between your dreams and reality
is hard work back by knowledge right
tune in to knowledge learn what you're
doing go out bust your ass pretty much
and get it done so what what do you
normally do for fun like what's sort of
things that you do for fun what do I do
for
fun well I hustle that's what I do for
fun man I don't I don't have I don't
really to be honest I don't have time
for fun I'm out achieving my dreams
right and what I do each and every day
with my business that is fun to me I'm
doing something to better my life I get
to do my lives I get to have fun
socializing with these other
entrepreneurs I get to go after my dream
I get to wake up every single day and
say I'm going to do something to better
my life and you know what Ryan that's
fun to me that's amazing to me so are
you telling me you don't have any
friends that you like you that that you
want to hang out with and like a
girlfriend that you just go out and and
chill out or are you just hustling all
all all all goddamn day I have I have
friends but I'm hustling man I'm
hustling that's my main focus I'm not
focused on hanging out with friends I'm
not f on none of that I'm hustling I
socialize with friends I still
communicate with friends I still you
know I still talk to friends but I'm
focused on my grind man like that's my
goal is just to give it 120% into my
grind so I can achieve my dreams later
on in my life that's right that's a
perfect example because I think that it
doesn't matter what age you are um when
it comes down to the hustle like you
know for me like for my birthday people
like what are you doing hustling right
you know like
if I want a million dollars what are you
doing today hustling because like it's
about the goals limit success has no age
limit that's right so you got to do you
got to grind you got to do it and you
know sometimes you got to take a break
and I realized that like in the last few
um months like I've kind of burnt myself
out probably aged a little bit too
because I've been like grinding grinding
grinding but you know what what when I
see the hustle Zone picking up and when
I see so many people around us that like
yourself everyone's kind of building
their brands and and whatnot based off
of the things that you know like others
people are doing like you know we could
mention Shane the train and Frank and
all these guys like you know now you're
popping up like they seeing this this
whole movement happened with with with
people um you know where everyone's like
if they feel that they have a voice they
have it and you know so right now it's
not time to sleep it's a time to get up
wake up until we actually ual the dreams
because just put it this way Stephen the
person that grinds the hardest is going
to be the one that wins don't you agree
yes yes and if you really want to get
right down to it Ryan you're spot on man
that's a fact you got to give it 120%
you got to go out and you got to hit it
with all you got and if you're not
hitting it with all you got you are not
going to be successful in life and I'm
talking truly successful everybody has a
different definition of success but you
got to give
120% to truly achieve what you call
successful so um final question uh what
makes you happy right now besides
hustling what makes me
happy uh my family makes me happy uh the
the love and support I get from my fans
from my from the people that are tuning
in to my live videos from the
entrepreneurs I'm associating with
people that build me up that makes me
happy just just you know life makes me
happy in general there's so much you
just mentioned earlier in the video
about how you can notice negativity and
everything yes that's true but there's
so much positivity too if we open our
eyes to it and and positivity man just
the fact that I'm I get a chance to live
on this Earth Chase my dreams go out
every day and get it and and just live
my life the way I want to man that makes
me happy yeah and uh so what what sort
of like what's your favorite dish what
do you like to eat would I like to eat
oh man lots of things man lots of things
from from Mexican dishes to Italian
dishes you know I like stuff like
lasagna enchiladas just just a number of
different things oh you like the ethnic
foods man like shot you like spicy foods
oh yeah and um you know in TW 10 years
from now where do you see
yourself I see my company with an office
I see myself
reaching at least 200,000 teenagers and
changing their lives by 10 years and and
what I mean by changing my lives is I
don't want to just teach them I want to
go out teach them completely change
their lives and give them the proper
training they need to go out get after
it and chase their dreams in and teach
others the steps to success and and
that's where my company goal is uh Ryan
is I'm going to have my own office I'm
going to uh just
uh at least impact 100,000 people I'm
going to be speaking at uh colleges
universities things like that and these
are goals that my company has within 10e
time well that's that's amazing so how
can we find you my friend I'm on
Facebook you can follow our Facebook
page Young Gun motivation very simply
spelled just young Space Gun space
motivation you can add me on Facebook
Steven Graber or you can check out my
website which is
www. young gunm motivation.com just like
and also I'm on YouTube Young Gun
motivation like subscribe and just hit
me up guys and uh give us a final word
to all the the children all the young
kids out there that are in your age
bracket like give us a a sermon give us
a last the last sermon and just pretend
that this is going to you know you
you're now Moving on but you just want
to leave one last message what would
that be put your blinders on put your
ear muffs in and do not listen to
anybody but one person right listen this
is what I did I found one coach One
Mentor which was Coach Frank sagasta of
course he introduced me to some other
people like uh like Grant Cardone like
Eric Thomas and them find a coach put
your e muffers on to anybody else right
put just completely block out everybody
except your Mentor listen to what he has
apply the information to your life and
just get out get after it and make it
happen massive effective action chase
your dreams go after it and really
that's the only way I can say like
straight up I leave it raw and real Ryan
is just go out get after it and make it
happen for your own life because
nobody's going to do it for you you got
to do it yourself okay well thank you so
much Stephen and I I I I I hope that we
can bring you back to the the hustle
Zone and anytime you have a a major
Milestone that you want to shout out
just hit me up and I'll get you back on
here because we want to see you succeed
we want to see your success so let us
know and and uh welcome Tuda well thank
you Ryan and oh you you didn't you
didn't know so if I say welcome Tuda I'm
G to do a call response you need to say
hustle Zone okay so welcome to the
hustle Zone hustle zone no no no we got
no no no that was whack that was whack
let's try that again welcome
to the hustle Zone there we go see what
I like folks we we film this stuff live
so once we edit this we're going to make
a collage of all the people that are
doing the the hustle zone so like this
is going to be live um I can't wait but
like this is the first dressed up show
we had a few little uh technical cakes
in in the show but either way uh this is
going to be the new the new set that
we're going to be using so hope you guys
enjoyed it uh Stephen I really liked uh
I really like your energy man I I really
like what you have to give uh you're
really determent it's almost like you've
been in the army or something like that
cuz you're like straight like serious
you're like man I'm going to succeed man
with the mission man and and and it
straight comes down to Ryan purpose I
have a purpose in life and I'm not going
to stop and CH I achieve that person
because I'm not a quitter I never been a
quitter and I will not quit until I
achieve what I want to achieve there you
go there you go so thank you so much my
friend and I will talk to you later
before we go we got a commercial and
then we're out
[Music]